AFSCME, District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series II: Executive Office Records, 1951-1999.
  - Subseries II:A: Stanley Hill Executive Director Records, 1987-1999.
    - New York City Budget: Summary and Message of the Mayor, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - New York City Budget Crisis and Layoffs I, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - New York City Budget Crisis and Layoffs II, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - New York City Budget Crisis and Layoffs: Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - New York City Budget Crisis and Layoffs: Printed Material, Jun 1905-1991 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - New York City Council, 1995, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - New York City Council, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - New York City Council: Medicaid Managed Care Hearings, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - New York City Department of Design and Construction, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - New York City Department of Environmental Protection, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - New York City Department of Health, 1991, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - New York City Department of Homeless Services: Camp LaGuardia, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - New York City Department of Information Technology and Telecommunications, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - New York City Department of Parks and Recreation, 1990-1991, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - New York City Department of Probation, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - New York City Department of Sanitation, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - New York City Department of Transportation, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - New York City Department of Transportation: Highway Seasonals, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - New York City Emergency Medical Service (EMS): Operating Guide I, ca.1991 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - New York City EMS: Operating Guide II, ca.1991 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - New York City Employees' Retirement System, 1990-1991, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - New York City Employees' Retirement System (Oversize), 1991 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC), 1987-1991, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - New York City HHC, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - New York City HHC: Board of Directors, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - New York City HHC: Executed Contracts, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - New York City HHC: Joint Committee on Accreditation, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - New York City HHC: Layoffs I, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - New York City HHC: Layoffs II, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - New York City HHC: Layoffs, Job Postings, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - New York City HHC: Layoffs, Lists of Terminated and Reinstated Employees, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - New York City HHC: Layoffs, Lists of Terminated and Reinstated Employees (Oversize), 1998 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - New York City Housing Authority, 1990, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - New York City Human Resources Administration, 1990-1991, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - New York City Human Resources Administration: Business Link, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - New York City Independent Budget Office, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - New York City Mayor's Management Advisory Task Force, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - New York City Mayor's Management Report, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - New York City Mayor's Private Sector Survey, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - New York City Office of Collective Bargaining, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - New York City Office of Labor Relations, 1990-1991, 1994, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - New York City Office of Medicaid Managed Care, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - New York City Office of the Comptroller, 1991, 1995, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - New York City Office of the Comptroller: Reports, 1990, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - New York City Office of the Comptroller: Transcripts of Economic Hearings, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - New York City Office of the Criminal Justice Coordinator, 1995, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - New York City Office of the Mayor, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - New York City Office of the Mayor: Press Releases, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - New York City Public Schools, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - New York City Public Schools (Oversize), 1991 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - New York City School Construction Authority, 1990, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health, 1991, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - New York Labor Committee against Apartheid, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - New York Police Department: 911 Settlement, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - New York State AFL-CIO, 1990-1991, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - New York State AFL-CIO: Legislative Issues, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - New York State AFL-CIO: Printed Material and Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - New York State AFL-CIO: Tax Proposal, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - New York State Assembly: Assembly Action Highlights, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - New York State Assembly: Committee Agendas, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - New York State Assembly: Correspondence, 1991, 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - New York State Assembly: Correspondence, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - New York State Assembly: Labor Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - New York State Assembly: HIV Notification ("Baby AIDS") Bill, 1994-1998 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - New York State Assembly: Press Releases and Printed Material I, 1991, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - New York State Assembly: Press Releases and Printed Material II, 1991, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - New York State Black and Puerto Rican Caucus, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - New York State Black and Puerto Rican Caucus, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - New York State Budget, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - New York State Budget: Coalition to Save New York, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - New York State Budget: Senate-Assembly Bills, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - New York State Children's Health Insurance Plan (CHIP), 1997 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - New York State Constitutional Convention, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - New York State Democratic Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - New York State Department of Health, 1990-1991, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - New York State Department of Labor, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - New York State Department of Labor: Press Releases, 1990-1991, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - New York State Department of Labor: Public Employee Health and Safety Bureau, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - New York State Department of Social Services, 1990, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - New York State Emergency Medical Service, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - New York State Financial Control Board, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - New York State Hospital Review and Planning Council, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - New York State Martin Luther King, Jr. Commission, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - New York State Nurses Association, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - New York State Office of the Comptroller, 1991, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - New York State Office of the Comptroller, 1995-1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - New York State Office of the Governor, 1994, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - New York State Office of the Governor: Press Releases, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - New York State School Food Service Association, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - New York State Senate: Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - New York State Senate: Printed Material and Reports, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - New York State Temporary Commission on Local Government Ethics, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Notes, 1991, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Notes: Meetings, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Unit, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 153, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Officers: List, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - One Hundred Black Men, Inc., 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - PEOPLE Committee, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Phone Message Log, 1990-1991, 1995, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Policy Development, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Political Action: Elections (City), 1990-1991, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Political Action: Elections (Congressional), 1990, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Political Action: Elections (State), 1990, 1994, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Political Action: Endorsements and Field Operations, 1991, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Political Action and Legislation Department, 1990-1991, 1996-1999 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Political Action and Legislation Department: Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Printed Material: Organizations, 1990-1991, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Printed Material: Other Unions, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Privatization: Contracting Out, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Privatization: Hospitals, 1991, 1996, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Professional Division: Correspondence, 1991, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Professional Division: Reports, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Public Relations and Publications Department: Correspondence, ca.1990-1991, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Public Relations and Publications Department: Media Alerts I, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Public Relations and Publications Department: Media Alerts II, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Public Relations and Publications Department: Media Alerts III, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Public Relations and Publications Department: Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Quality of Work Life Program, 1990-1991, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Queens Hospital Center: Privatization of Cafeteria Services, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Rainbow/Push Coalition, 1991, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Real Estate Department: Correspondence, 1990-1997 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Real Estate Department: Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Regional Plan Association, 1990, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Research and Negotiations Department: Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Research and Negotiations Department: Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Retiree Association, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Schedules and Calendars, 1990-1991, 1996, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Schools Division, 1990-1991, 1996-1998 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Speeches, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Staff Complaints and Grievances, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Staff Lists, 1992-1997 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Task Force on Medicaid Services and Cost Containment, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Television Transcripts, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - United Negro College Fund, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - United States Congress, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Walk the Walk, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Welfare Fund, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Welfare Funds: New York State Comptroller's Report, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Welfare Reform, 1996-1998 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - White Collar Division: Reports, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Woodhull Health Care Network, ca.1990s (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Work Experience Program (Workfare), 1995-1999 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Workplace AIDS Advisory Board I, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Workplace AIDS Advisory Board II, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Subseries II:B: Lillian Roberts Associate Director Records, 1951-1983.
    - Ad Hoc Coordinating Committee for a City-Wide Coalition to Save our Public Schools, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Addiction Services Agency: Budget Reductions, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Africa: AFSCME Delegation and Fund to Aid African Trade Unionists I, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Africa: AFSCME Delegation and Fund to Aid African Trade Unionists II, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Africa: AFSCME Delegation and Fund to Aid African Trade Unionists, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Africa: Financial Assistance Requests, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Africa: Printed material, ca.1972 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Africa: Public Services International Conference, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Africa: Public Services International Labor Tour I, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Africa: Public Services International Labor Tour II, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Africa: Public Services International Seminar, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Africa: Public Services International Seminar, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Africa Tour, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Afro-Asian Institute Associates (Histadrut), 1980 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - AFSCME, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - AFSCME, Council 50 (New York State Employees), 1969-1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - AFSCME: Staff Intern Program, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - AFSCME: "There's Strength in Numbers Campaign", 1973 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Alcohol Program for City of New York Employees, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - American Arbitration Association: Commercial Panel, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - American Committee on Africa (ACOA), 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - American Public Health Association, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - American Voter Education Fund, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Amsterdam News: Series on New York City Employees, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Appointment Book, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Appointment Book, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Beame, Abraham: Health Advisory Task Force, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Bellevue Hospital, 1973-1978 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Bellevue Hospital Employees' Advisory Council, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Bio-Medical Equipment Technical Training Program, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Blue Collar Division: Monthly Reports, May 1974-Sep 1974 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Blue Collar Division: Monthly Reports, Oct 1974-Feb 1975 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Blue Collar Division: Monthly Reports, Mar 1975-Nov 1975 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Blue Collar Locals: Citywide Strike, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Borough of Manhattan Community College Fund, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Bronx Municipal Hospital Center, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Bryan (David E.) Fund, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Career Development and Training, 1968-1971 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Career Development and Training, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Career Development and Training: Hospitals I, 1967-1972 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Career Development and Training: Hospitals II, 1967-1972 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Career Development and Training: Hospitals III, 1967-1972 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Carver Federal Savings: Board of Directors, 1974-1981 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - CUNY: Career Programs, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Clerical-Administrative Division: Monthly Reports, Apr 1974-Nov 1974 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Clerical-Administrative Division: Monthly Reports, Dec 1974-May 1975 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Clerical-Administrative Division: Monthly Reports, Jun 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, 1973-1979 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Coalition of Concerned Citizens for Human Resources, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Coalition of Trade Union Women, 1974-1978 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - College of New Rochelle DC 37 Campus, New Resources Program, 1973-1975, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Committee of Interns and Residents, undated, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Committee of Interns and Residents: Effects of Personnel Reductions in Hospitals, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Committee to Aid the Refugees of East Pakistan, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Community Mental Health Center, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Community School Board Elections, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA), Oct 1978-Apr 1979 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - CETA, May 1979-Jun 1979 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - CETA, Jul 1979-Aug 1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - CETA, Sep 1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - CETA, Oct 1979-Mar 1980 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - CETA Questionnaire, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Contracting Out: Hospitals, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Sep 1971-Dec 1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1972-Mar 1972 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Apr 10, 1972-Jun 1972 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1972-Oct 1972 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Oct 1972-Dec 1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1973-Jun 1973 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1974-May 1974 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1977-Jun 1977 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1977-Dec 1977 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1978-Mar 1978 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Apr 1978-May 1978 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1978 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1978-Dec 1978 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1979-May 1979 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1979-Sep 1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Oct 1979-Dec 1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1981-Feb 1981 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Mar 1981-Jun 1981 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Coney Island Hospital, 1976-1979 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Cost of Living Adjustment (COLA): Clerical Division, ca.1975 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Council for the Advancement of Experiential Learning (CAEL), 1977-1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Cumberland Hospital, 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Cumberland Hospital Mental Health Service, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Daycare Programs, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Delafield Hospital: Action to Prevent Closing, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Delafield Hospital: Legal Papers, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Democratic National Party Conference: Platform Advisory Committee, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Education Fund, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Education Fund, 1976-1979 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Educational Guidance Center for the Retarded, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Emergency Employment Act of 1971 I, 1971-1974 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Emergency Employment Act of 1971 II, 1971-1974 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Emergency Medical Services: Safety Conditions and Training, 1972-1976 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Executive Staff, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Federation of Field Representatives, 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Federation of Field Representatives, 1975-1981 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Federation of Field Representatives: Agreements, 1970-1980 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Feed the Hungry Drive, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Budget Meetings with City Departments, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Fordham Hospital, undated, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Ghetto Medicine Program (New York State), 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Goldwater Hospital Parking Facility Closing, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Gouverneur Hospital, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Gouverneur Hospital, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Harlem Hospital, 1975-1979 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Harlem Hospital: Community-Worker Board, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Health and Security Plan: Option IV, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Help Our Own Fund (for laid-off members), 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - High Risk Premature Infant Technician Training Program, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - HIP of Greater New York, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Home Attendants, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Hospital Closings and Layoffs, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Hospitals Division: Monthly Reports, Apr 1974-Nov 1974 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Housekeeping Aid Sanitation Training Program, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - I Paid My Dues (labor play), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - International Conference on Trends in Industrial Relations (Tel Aviv, Israel), 1971 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Interns, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Invitations, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Just One Break (JOB), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: DC 37 Response to Assassination and Tributes, 1968-1978 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Kings County Hospital Center, 1973-1978 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Kings County Hospital Center: Attitudinal Program, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Legal Internship and Training Education (LITE) Program: Bedford Stuyvesant Lawyers Association, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Legal Services Proposal, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Legislative Information, 1969-1971, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Lincoln Hospital, 1971-1978 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Local 154 (Amalgamated Professional Employees), 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Local 371 (SSEU), 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Local 371(SSEU), 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Local 371 (SSEU), 1977-1981 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Local 371 (SSEU): Contract, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Local 371 (SSEU): Dental Assistants, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Local 371 (SSEU): Homemakers and Housekeepers, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education), 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education), 1975 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education), 1976-1981 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): Career Training Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): Hourly Workers, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): New York Archdiocese Schools, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): Para-Professionals, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Local 375 (CSTG), 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Local 375 (CSTG), 1977-1980 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Local 384 (CUNY): Gittelson Employees, 1951-1980 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), Jan 1968-Apr 1968 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), May 1968-Jul 1968 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), Aug 1968-Dec 1968 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), Jan 1969-May 1969 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), Jun 1969-Dec 1969 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1970 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1975 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1977-Aug 1980 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), Sep 1980-Apr 1981 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Ambulance Technicians, 1969-1972 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): James Butler Dispute, 1978-1980 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): James Butler Dispute, Petitions and Legal Papers, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Bonano v. Butler, Release Time Information, 1976-1979 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Delegates Election I, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Delegates Election II, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 9)